OP
ED
AAA
Takahama
I got my serialization! I couldn't have done it without your help!
AAA
Takahama
おかげさまで 連載決まりました
We just heard the news from Hattori.
はい さっき服部さんから聞いたところです
Congratulations!
おめでとうございます
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
We can finally compete against each other with our serializations!
いよいよ 連載で勝負ですね
My first order of business is to beat you!
僕の当面の目標は 亜城木先生に勝つ事です
He just declared war on us.
宣戦布告されちゃった
First Fukuda, and now Takahama.
高浜さんに福田さん 面白くなってきたな
Things keep getting more and more interesting.
We need to work hard so that we don't lose!
負けないように 頑張ろうぜ
Yeah!
NATURAL is 4th in the final ranking!
本ちゃん
「NATURAL」4位 変わらず
It didn't change.
Damn.
くそっ
6th isn't good enough!
6位じゃ駄目なんだ
ano ne moshimo ima sugu ni kimi no moto he to
Hey, if I could go to where you are right now
话说       如果现在马上飞奔到你身边
ikeru naraba kono koe ga nakunattemo ii ya
then I could accept losing my voice
能实现的话 失去声音也无所谓
mezasu basho ga amari ni mo tooku
The goals I've set myself seem impossible to reach,
目标太过遥远     我似乎已经迷失方向了
boku wa mou michi ni mayoisou da
and I feel lost on my path
kowareta jishaku wo ate ni shiteru n da
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in another's shadow
让损坏了的指南针仍能奏效 就隐藏在谁的影子之下
dareka no kage ni kakurete sa
nanika wo te ni ireru tame nanika wo tebanasu nante koto wo
If we keep letting go of some things in order to find something else,
为了得到什么就必须放弃什么
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
继续下去我们也一定不会长大
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
narenai
Never
不会长大
Every Night and Unite
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神字幕组---
台本:共由先生         翻译:   poopy    虫    繁化:烨语
校对：绫女      后期：福尔摩斯的手杖
每晚与融合
All right. I'll be there to pick up the manuscript in a bit.
ああ 分かった 今から原稿 取りに行くから
Let's have the meeting for GIRI there, too.
「GIRI」の打ち合わせも そこでやっちゃおう
Man, this feels great!
いやあ 気持ちいい
We're already preparing for our next
serialization and KIYOSHI hasn't even ended yet!
「KIYOSHI」終わってないのに 次の連載 決まりなんて
かっこよすぎだろ
Speaking of, did you manage to find an assistant who can draw motorbikes?
そういや バイク描けるアシは見つかったんですか
Nope, not yet.
それはまだ
When it comes to motorcycle drag racing, I guess you could say that I drag my feet!
モータースポーツだけに モタついちゃって
Um, Yuujirou...
あの 雄二郎さん
Hattori's been acting a little strange.
服部先輩がおかしいんです
He said that 6th place isn't good enough for PCP.
「PCP」6位じゃ駄目なんて言って
But 6th place is pretty good.
順調じゃないですか
PCP is a special case.
「PCP」は特別枠だからな
How is it a special case?
特別枠
It's one of those "unspoken agreements".
暗黙の了解ってやつだよ
PCP is really getting responses.
「PCP」には 正直 手応えがある
I can't just let it get canceled...
それを みすみす
Are you listening to me?!
話 聞いてますか
Oh, sorry.
ああ すまない
Please take this more seriously!
もっと真面目に やって下さい
I absolutely cannot afford to lose to Ashirogi Mutou!
私は絶対に 亜城木夢叶には負けられないんです
It'll be fine.
大丈夫だ
Within six months, PCP will probably be...
半年後には 「PCP」は多分
6th place isn't good enough.
6位では 駄目なんだ
If PCP isn't on equal footing with CROW and NATURAL within the next six months...
「PCP」は半年以内に「CROW」「NATURAL」と競うくらいになっていなければ
it'll be canceled.
打ち切られる
What?
Those were the conditions.
そういう条件を出されている
It's not that surprising, is it?
驚く事じゃないだろ
When we ended Tanto...
「タント」やめる時に
We'll beat Niizuma Eiji.
新妻エイジに勝ってみせます
So please let us end Tanto!
だから 「タント」は終わりにさせて下さい
Oh, that's right!
ああ そうだった
I kept quiet about it because I didn't want to put more pressure on you.
余計なプレッシャーは与えない方が と黙っていたが
But if we leave things as they are,
このまま何も手を打たないと
PCP will be canceled.
打ち切りになる
NATURAL's anime begins in April.
4月には 「NATURAL」のアニメ開始
Fukuda and the others' new
serializations will enter the picture, too.
福田君たちの新連載も入ってくるからな
Sounds like it'll be tough.
厳しいですね
We'll have to be competitive against Eiji and Iwase despite all that.
その中で エイジ 岩瀬と競う
We need to at least get to 3rd place.
少なくとも3位くらいにまで上がらなければ
PCP will end?
「PCP」は終わる
It's off the record, but it's true.
表立った話ではないが そういう事らしい
That kind of condition isn't right!
そんな条件 おかしいじゃないですか
The harder I try, the more Takagi has to...
私が 頑張れば頑張るほど 高木君たちは
Doesn't this work to your advantage?
むしろ好都合じゃないか
You wanted to beat PCP, didn't you?
「PCP」を蹴落としたかったんだろ
Akina...
秋名君 もしかして
Do you actually enjoy competing with Takagi?
高木君と競ってる事が楽しい うれしいんじゃないのか
Does it make you happy?
O-Of course not!
ち 違います
It's important for Takagi be there so that I can be above him!
高木君がいて その上に私がいる事が大切なんです
Well, there's no need to worry about them ranking higher than NATURAL.
ま まあ 高木君たちが「NATURAL」の上に行く心配は しなくてもいい
What do you mean?
どういう意味ですか
I just came from Niizuma's place, and...
さっき 新妻君の所にも行ってきたんだが
Then Ashirogi's manga will be canceled.
じゃあ 亜城木先生終わっちゃうじゃないですか
So you feel the same way, huh?
やっぱり そうなるのか
Yes.
はい 今のままの「PCP」には負ける気がしません
I don't think we'll lose against PCP as it is now.
When it comes to manga, Niizuma is always right.
マンガに関しては 新妻君の言う事は当たる
Hattori even says he's psychic.
服部先輩に言わせれば エスパーだ
Niizuma said, "As it is now," right?
その新妻さんが 今のままではと
Yeah.
Call Takagi, and then give me the phone!
高木君に電話して 私に代わりなさい
Huh?!
Do it now!
今すぐ
O-Okay!
は はいっ
We can't keep going on like this.
普通にやっていては駄目だ
We have to find some way to kick it up a notch.
確実に もうワンランクアップさせる手段を
Excuse me for a minute.
ちょっと すみません
Miura Gorou
Miura?
港浦さん
港浦
This is Iwase.
岩瀬です
Iwase?!
えっ 岩瀬 な 何で
Why are you...
I need to apologize.
謝ります
I planned on using every trick in the book to beat you two.
どんな手を使ってでもあなたたちを蹴落とすつもりでいましたが
However,
I've decided that this approach is ridiculous.
そんな愚かな考えは捨てます
From now on, we'll compete fair and square, using only our manga!
これからは 正々堂々と作品で戦います
Do you understand me? You two can't beat us as you are now!
いいですか
このままでは あなたたちは 私たちに勝てない
H-Hold on! I'm not following you at all.
ちょっ ちょっと待て さっきから言ってる事 全然
Niizuma said it himself.
新妻さんが言ったそうです
He doesn't see PCP as a challenge as it is now.
今のままの「PCP」には負ける気がしないと
Eiji did?
エイジが
Think! Scheme! Use everything you've got!
考えなさい 工夫しなさい 全力を尽くしなさい
If you lose to me like this,
これで私に負けたら それは才能で負けたという事です
you'll have nothing to blame but your lack of talent!
Understand?!
いいですか
Iwase...
岩瀬
I understand.
分かった お前の言うとおり
You're exactly right.
Now that you've gone ahead and said all that...
ここまで教えてもらったんだ
we'll have to beat you!
抜いてみせる
I'd like to see you try.
できるものなら やってみなさい
Eiji and Iwase...
エイジに岩瀬
We've got some good rivals.
いいライバル 持ったな
Yeah!
I'm taking a break! Nothing you say can stop me, Mr. Yoshida!
もう 僕は休む
吉田氏が何と言おうともだ
Oh? What if I said that I'd cancel your tea date with Aoki?
では 休んだら蒼樹さんとのお茶会は無しだと言ったら
Tea?!
お 茶 会
Y-You finally set up the tea party with Aoki?!
ついに蒼樹さんとの お茶会セッティングを
Of course I did!
そうともさ
And it'll be here.
しかも場所は ここ
Mr. Yoshida!
よ 吉田氏
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Pledge Regarding Tea Party
Hiramaru Kazuya (henceforth known as Person A)
and Yoshida Kouji (henceforth known as Person B)
will sign this pledge regarding Person A's manga
Otter no.11 in accordance with the following terms.
All you need to do is sign this.
では ここに サインを
Mr. Yoshida, why are we having tea here?
吉田氏 何で ここでお茶会を
Don't you want to show off your
unusually large and chic living room?
無駄に広く かっこいいリビングを使わない手はないだろ
Oh, luxury apartments!
ああ デザイナーズマンション
Aren't you glad that you took out that huge loan?
高いローン 払ってきてよかったな
Yeah.
はいっ
You should probably finish your manuscript before the tea date.
お茶会までに 原稿 仕上げなきゃな
Yeah.
はいっ
Now that you have something to look forward to, you won't take a break from Otter, right?
こんなにいい事があったら「ラッコ」休むなんて言えないな
Right!
はいっ
Yes!
よし これで もう半年
That should last us another six months.
PCP - Perfect Crime Party
Popular series! Ashirogi Mutou
So he doesn't think he'll lose against PCP as it is now?
今のままの「PCP」には 負ける気がしないか
Right.
はい
So PCP would stand a chance if we made changes to it.
今のままでなければ「PCP」が勝てる
Is that how we should interpret it?
そうも取れますよね
Yeah.
そうだな
That may have been the entire reason Niizuma phrased it that way.
新妻君も意識しているからこそ そんな事を言ったんだろう
By the way, you said that PCP is more popular with readers below the age of 10 and above the age of 18, right?
そういえば「PCP」は10歳以下と18歳以上でより票を取ってるって言ってましたよね
Basically, in a day they
would do 5-6 m. If they couldn't manage it,
they'd do 10 m the next day.
The only day they rested was the 16th.
The entrance was
made narrow enough to not
be found,
but you can walk inside upright.
In other words, a 108/65m
tunnel, huh.
It took six
years?
In my opinion, it's a hit with kids, and it
reminds adults of their childhood dreams.
僕の考えでは 子供は感心し
大人は 昔の自分と重ね 夢を感じる
It doesn't seem to be doing well among middle and high school readers.
中高生は少し冷めた見方という感じか
Why don't we make the Party's actions more flashy then?
じゃあ ＰＡＲＴＹの行動を もっと派手に
That's fine, but you have to make sure they're grounded in reality.
それはいいが
Crow
Wow!
現実で可能な範囲 日常から逸脱しない程度にしないと
Crow
Wow!
Don't deviate from things that are possible in normal, everyday life.
Crow
Wow!
You're right.
そうなんですよね
This isn't a battle manga, so we have to limit ourselves.
そこが バトルマンガと違うから どうしても限界が
Even if we don't have our answer right now, there's still six months left.
今すぐ答えが出なくても
半年以内お盆の合併号くらいに
By the time the Obon special issue is released, we need to be on an equal footing with Niizuma's manga.
新妻さんの作品と競えてればいいんですよね
Exactly.
そういう事になる
Damn it!
くっそ エイジには分かってるってのに
Even though I get what Eiji is saying...
I'll just have to read and analyze every popular manga we have from cover to cover!
こうなったら 大人気マンガを片っ端から読み込んで 分析してみます
March
Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thu
Fri
Sat
Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thu
Fri
Sat
Sun
Manuscript UP
8th Chapter
7th Chapter
あっ 真城さん 62番とグラデ系のトーン 残り少ないですよ
Mashiro, we're running low on #62 gradient tone.
Already?
もう
Well, I am applying it the way you instructed me to.
「もう」って
真城さんの指示で貼ってるんですから
If you don't realize just how much that uses up...
どのくらい使ってるか把握してもらわないと
All right. I'll order some more.
そうですね 補充しておきます
May I say something?
あの いいですか
As someone who went to design school,
デザイン系の専門行ってた者として言わせてもらうと
I believe you're relying too much on screentone.
少しトーンに頼りすぎです
Overusing it will actually result in a lack of depth.
使いすぎると 逆に立体感がなくなります
U-Um...
え えっと
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
A woman alone in a man's room.
女の子が一人で男の子の部屋に
That's quite risky, you know.
危険 危ないですよ
Your claim that we can't lose to PCP the way it is now piqued my interest.
今のままの「PCP」には負ける気がしない
そう言われたというのが気になって
That's right. We can't lose.
はい 負けません
PCP is too plain.
今の「PCP」は地味ですから
Plain?
地味
I suppose you're right. Its story is plain compared to that of a battle manga.
そうですね 決して バトルマンガのような派手さはない 地味なストーリー
No, not the story. I was talking about the art.
いえ ストーリーではなく 絵の方です
The art?
絵
Hey...
あのさ
Don't you think PCP is a bit dark?
「PCP」って 画面が暗いと思わない
Are you doing too much inking and screentoning?
ベタとトーンの使いすぎか
I didn't mean it like... Well, I might be, but...
そうじゃなくて
まあ それもあるんだけど
I don't think it feels like a shounen manga.
なんか少年マンガらしくないっていうか
The premise alone makes it different.
話自体 ちょっと色が違うじゃん
That's our unique characteristic.
それが俺たちの持ち味なんじゃ
No. It's a shounen manga, so I need to lighten it up.
いや 少年マンガなんだから 明るくしなきゃ駄目なんだと思う
In all of the popular manga up
until now, even the realistic ones,
今までの人気マンガだって
たとえ リアル系の作品でも
there were parts where the style
became lighter and more refreshing.
必ず読み味は明るくて スカッとするところがある
PCP's story is realistic, so the art should be, too.
「PCP」は 話がリアルだから 絵もリアルな方がいい
But it's still a manga.
でも マンガなんですから
I can't just draw everything realistically!
全てを リアルに描いたんじゃ 駄目なんだ
I have to put in plenty of expressions that you can only find in manga!
マンガにしかできない表現をふんだんに盛り込まないと
Sometimes artistic! Flashy!
時には アーティスティックに
ポップに
Stylish!
スタイリッシュに
Like this! Do you understand?
こんな感じです 分かります？
That's enough, Niizuma.
新妻さん もういいです
I didn't come here to ask you what Ashirogi Mutou lacks.
私は 亜城木夢叶に足りないものを聞きに来たのではありません
Huh? You didn't?
えっ そうなんです？
I came here to ask you not to tell them.
それを彼らに教えないよう 口止めに来たんです
Since you seem to be fond of them for some reason.
何か新妻さん 亜城木夢叶に甘いようなので
Because I'm their fan!
ファンですから
Regardless, I'd appreciate it if you didn't give them any advice.
だからといって 助言のような事はしてほしくありません
Of course, even if you did, I doubt we'd lo—
もちろん それで負けるとは思いませんが
I understand! I don't want to lose, either!
分かりました 僕だって負けたくありません
Let's make +NATURAL even more popular than it is now!
「+NATURAL」もっと人気マンガにしましょう
You're talented, so I know you have what it takes!
秋名さんは才能あるし できます
I-I'm talented?
さ 才能
Yes!
はい
You're dropping out of college?!
大学 辞める
I don't need a degree or a backup plan anymore.
もう肩書も保険も要らない
What I need now is time to improve my art.
今 必要なのは絵を上達させる時間
I already convinced my parents and texted Azuki about it.
親も説得したし 亜豆にもメールで伝えた
I see.
そうか
We are serialized right now, after all.
連載しながらだもんな
This was one
heck of a hem stitch!
Then how about this stitched strap!
Saikou, I know you said you'd make changes gradually,
サイコー 徐々に変えてくって言ってたけど
but chapter eight is already looking very different.
この8話目 随分 印象変わったな
Really?
そう
Chapters five and six are in 7th place.
5話6話と7位
Chapter seven is in 8th place.
7話は8位
We'll be in trouble if we lose any more ground to Niizuma.
これ以上 新妻君と離されるとやばい
I hope making the art lighter in chapter eight shows some results.
絵を明るめに変えたこの8話で 何とか
えっ 本ちゃん5位
We're 5th in the final ranking?!
And by a close margin to NATURAL?!
それも 「NATURAL」に僅差で
It really went up!
随分 上がりましたね
So it really wasn't the story, but the art.
やっぱりストーリーじゃなく 絵だった
I'm still making changes through trial and error,
まだ 試行錯誤しながらだけど
but if I keep this up...
このまま続けていけば
The editorial department said that PCP's
improvement in this week's rankings must be a fluke.
編集部的には 今回「PCP」が少し上がったのはたまたまだろうと
Then the editorial department isn't paying enough attention to PCP.
編集部 ちゃんと「PCP」見てませんね
We'll be in even more trouble by next week.
次は もっとやばいですよ
How so?
やばい このままだと「NATURAL」どころか
If this keeps up...
it won't only overtake NATURAL, but CROW, too.
「CROW」も抜かれます
Ashirogi is changing their art style.
亜城木先生 絵を変えてきてます
It's even better in their ninth chapter in this sample copy.
見本誌の9話目は更に良くなってます
Is that why you did something different with the manuscript than what we discussed last week?
それで先週の原稿は打ち合わせと違う あんな事を
Yup. I redrew the whole thing after seeing PCP's eighth chapter.
はい 「PCP」の8話目を見て描き直しました
But that'll let them overtake us even faster...
しかし あれじゃそれこそ抜かれるんじゃ
That won't happen.
それはないです
The gap between us might close after
Ashirogi sees that manuscript, though.
あの原稿を亜城木先生が見てからは 差を縮めてくるかもしれませんけど
Akina?
秋名君
Is Miura not with you?
あれ 港浦は
I came here alone today.
今日は一人で来ました
Zoom out here!
ここで ズームアウト
And pretend to...
えっ この2人
Are these two...
This reminds me of when she asked Hattori what he thought of her as a woman.
そういえば 服部 秋名君に女性として どうかって迫られたって
She's not going after Niizuma now, is she?
まさか 新妻君にも
Nah, I'm probably reading too much into this.
いや 考えすぎだな
You seem to be taking your time with CROW.
「CROW」 随分 時間かけて描かれているんですね
Yes!
イエース
Will +NATURAL be okay?
「+NATURAL」の方大丈夫だと思います
What do you mean?
何がです
PCP won't overtake it in the rankings, right?
「PCP」に抜かれないかです
We'll probably lose to PCP's chapter nine in the immediate rankings when that issue goes on sale next week.
次週発売の9話目は速報で負けると思うです
Niizuma Eiji is always right.
新妻エイジの言う事は当たる
But +NATURAL's anime starts that Tuesday!
けど その火曜から「+NATURAL」 アニメスタート
So we'll put up a fight in the final rankings!
ですから 本ちゃんではいい勝負になります
Ashirogi is changing their art style bit by bit.
亜城木先生絵を少しずつ変えてきてます
So CROW must go even higher than PCP!
だから「CROW」は「PCP」の更に上を行きます
I won't lose!
絶対に負けません
Damn! PCP overtook us!
やばい 「PCP」に抜かれてる
The color illustration on the cover celebrating the start of the anime didn't do a thing.
せっかく アニメ記念の巻頭カラーなのに
Damn it!
くっそ
PCP is in 4th,
「PCP」4位
just one place ahead of NATURAL in the immediate rankings.
速報は「NATURAL」の1つ上か
But...
しかし
Watch out!
危ない
It's being born.
生まれる
I-I hate to admit it, but this is good.
く 悔しいけど面白いかも
Yeah. The kids are sure to vote for this.
ああ これは子供票入るな
The anime that Azuki could've had a role in...
亜豆が出演していたかもしれなかったアニメ
I have to make PCP an anime for her sake, too!
亜豆のためにも 必ず「PCP」をアニメに
+NATURAL!
「+NATURAL」
Just as Niizuma predicted, we lost to PCP in the immediate rankings.
新妻さんの言ったとおり
速報では「PCP」に負けた
Let's make +NATURAL even more popular than it is now!
「+NATURAL」もっと人気マンガにしましょう
You're talented, so I know you have what it takes!
秋名さんは才能あるし できます
This country's clams really are delicious!
やっぱりこの国のハマグリは うまい
Hikaru Fishery's Clam Pack!
ヒカル水産ハマグリパック
Promotional giveaway in collaboration with Otter no. 11!
「ラッコ11号」コラボキャンペーン実施中
Otter No. 11
Promotional campaign
collaboration
110,000 lucky winners will receive Otter no. 11 limited edition figures!
抽選で 11万名様に「ラッコ11号」限定フィギュアを プレゼント
Clam
This is adorable!
かわいい
Thank you, Hiramaru!
平丸先生 ありがとうございます
Isn't this great? You would go on about how you
wanted one every time that commercial came on.
よかったね 限定フィギュア ＣＭ見る度に欲しいって言ってたもんね
It is!
はい
Thank you so much.
いつも すみません
Oh, this is nothing.
いやあ これくらいどうって事ありませんよ
How does it taste? I bought that Earl Grey myself.
どうですか 僕がこの手で 仕入れてきた アールグレイのお味は
I'm sorry. I always drink Darjeeling, so my opinion on Earl Grey would be...
ごめんなさい 私はいつも ダージリンなので
アールグレイの味は
Darjeeling?
ダージリン
M-Mr. Yoshida, can I speak to you in the other room?
よ 吉田氏 ちょっと隣の部屋へ
Yamashita.
山久
Yes?
はい
You bastard! You told me that Aoki likes Earl Grey!
貴様 蒼樹さんはアールグレイが好きって言ったよな
The aroma of Earl Grey is perfect for this chilly weather, don't you think?
アールグレイは このかんきつ系の香りがいいですよね
I'm rather fond of Darjeeling, myself. I drank it pretty often back home.
ダージリンも好きで 実家で よく飲んでました
That muscatel flavor is very nice.
マスカテルフレーバー いいですね
You're quite knowledgeable.
随分 お詳しいんですね
Oh, not at all.
いや それほどでも
Niizuma, here's the sample copy of next week's issue of Jack.
新妻君 これ 来週の「ジャック」の見本誌
Thanks!
どうもです
Your art is amazing and all, but can you not do this again?
絵が すごいのは分かるが
こういうのはこれっきりにしてくれよ
Roger!
ラジャー
By the way, NATURAL placed 4th in the final rankings.
そういや 「NATURAL」の本ちゃん 4位
After the anime started, it overtook PCP.
アニメ始まって 「PCP」に逆転したって
Did Miura already tell you?
もう 港浦から聞いた
Yes. It's just as I expected.
はい 思ったとおりでした
Akina again?
また 秋名君か
Probably.
ですね
Just how often has she been coming over?
こんな頻繁に来てるのか
Pretty much every day this week.
今週に入ってからは大体 毎日ですけど
N-Niizuma!
に 新妻君
The two of you are grown adults.
君も秋名君も大人だ
I don't mean to be crude, but please take it more slowly!
やぼな事は言いたくないが ほどほどにしとけよな な
Please!
What are you talking about?
何をほどほどにするです
And I'll be a boy forever. That's why I draw shounen manga.
それに僕は 永遠の少年だから 少年マンガ 描いてるんですけど
R-Right.
What?! Aren't they practically living together, then?!
それ 通い妻ってやつじゃ
Keep your voice down, idiot!
バカ 大きな声 出すな
Sorry.
す すみません
But Akina's doing this every night?
でも あの秋名君が
しかも 毎晩なんて まずいですよね
This is bad.
You're her editor.
秋名君の担当は お前だろ
Get over here and talk to her about this.
ちょっと来て うまく注意してやってくれないか
What? No way! She won't listen to a word I have to say when it comes to love.
えっ そんな 恋愛面で僕の言う事なんか聞くとは
Just get over here!
いいから 来い
Yeah, they kind of give off that feeling...
確かに この雰囲気は
Niizuma, did you tell them that I was trying to entice you?
新妻さん 私が口説いていると教えたんですか
I haven't said anything.
何も教えてませんけど
Here's the sample copy of issue 20 with chapter ten of PCP.
「PCP」10話 20号の見本誌だ
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Take a look at CROW first.
とりあえず 「CROW」を見てくれ
CROW?
「CROW」
There isn't any dialogue!
セリフがない
He's telling the story with art alone!
絵だけで ストーリーを
After seeing PCP's eighth chapter, I heard that Eiji went back and completely redrew this chapter of CROW.
「PCP」の8話目を見て 新妻君はすぐにこの見せ方に切り替えたそうだ
He realized that I was starting to change my art style.
僕が絵を変え始めたのに気づいて
He's saying, "Look at how well I can tell the story with art alone!
自分は絵で ここまで作品を表現できる
Can you do the same?"
お前は どこまで できる そう言われてるとしか
I'm sure of it!
But can he stay popular like this?
でも これで人気取れるんですか
He's certainly taking a risk.
確かに冒険だな
Without any dialogue, the readers may feel something is lacking, and the number of votes may slightly decrease.
読者は セリフがない事で 物足りなさを感じて 少し票は下がると思うが
This is something he wanted to show me, even if it meant risking the loss of a few votes!
少しくらい人気が下がったとしても
僕に見せつけたかったって事か
No way! The chapter without any dialogue got more votes?!
ええっ セリフなしの回 票を上げたんですか
Yeah. I was surprised, too.
ああ 僕も驚いたよ
Normally, it'd get less.
普通なら下がる
But when Niizuma did it, he managed to convince the readers that it was an amazing and novel idea.
しかし 新妻君がやると 斬新かつすごいと読者を納得させてしまった
Eiji's surpassed me in both art and votes now.
エイジは 絵も票数も 僕より更に上に
NATURAL, on the other hand, didn't advance like I thought it would. It's still in 4th place.
それより 「NATURAL」が思ったより伸びない 今週も4位
PCP came in at 5th by 9 votes.
「PCP」は9票差で5位だ
9 votes?!
9票差
So close!
な 惜っしい
For the next three weeks, three new
serializations will start, one after the other.
次から新連載が3週連続で入ってくるが
Then during the following week in issue 26, PCP will get a full-color cover spread for its 15th chapter.
それから1週おいた26号
「PCP」15話目で 表紙と巻頭カラーだ
Full-color cover spread?
巻頭カラー
Really?!
本当ですか
We'll bet everything on that chapter!
ここで勝負をかける
Let's rank higher than NATURAL!
「NATURAL」の上を行くぞ
Right!
はい
I'll write the best story I can for chapter 15 of issue 26!
26号 15話目に 最高の話を用意してみせます
And I'll draw something for the cover and title page that far surpasses anything I've done before!
僕も表紙と扉のカラー 今まで以上のものを描いてみせます
What do you mean?
どういう事だ
With mutual consent between Niizuma and Akina...
新妻君と秋名君の合意で
Could they be getting married?!
まさか 結婚とか
Niizuma and Akina?
新妻君と秋名君か想像もつかんが
It's hard to imagine, but maybe those with true talent are attracted to each other.
あるいは互いの才能に惹かれ合って
Should we tell them to stop?
では やめさせろと
I never said that.
そうは言ってない
Does Niizuma have a problem with it?
新妻君も納得しているのか
Honestly, I get the feeling that Akina forcefully persuaded him into it.
正直 秋名君が 強引に口説き落としたって感じですが
But after the fact, Niizuma seemed extremely excited about it.
その後は 新妻君もまんざらじゃなく積極的に
I see.
そうか
Then there's no problem here.
それなら問題はないだろう
Th-Thank you!
あ ありがとうございます
Takahama's new serialization is good!
高浜さんの新連載 面白いな
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Yeah.
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
Shounen Jack
SHOCKING!
Trial battles!
Court
sessions!
Seigi no mikata
Takahama Shoyo
He managed to make a shounen
manga out of a courtroom setting.
ああ 裁判ものなのに ちゃんと少年マンガになってる
All right, Road Racer GIRI!
おっしゃ 「ロードレーサーGIRI」本ちゃん1位
1st place in the final rankings!
I'll keep on tearing through the competition!
このまま ぶっちぎってやるぜ
Fukuda is amazing!
福田さん すげな
The energy in the second chapter is just as high as in the first!
2話目も めちゃくちゃテンション高え
And it really shows that Takahama's done his homework on courtrooms.
高浜さんも法廷の描写とか すごく勉強してるよ
Seigi no Mikata
Seigi no Mikata's first chapter got 3rd place, and the second and third chapter were at 7th.
「正義の三肩」 1話3位で
Seigi no Mikata
2話3話7位
He's been right behind us the entire time.
Seigi no Mikata
僕たちのすぐあとに ずっとつけてる
Yeah, even though last week's new serialization dropped to 11th place with its second chapter.
ああ 先週の新連載は2話目11位に落ちたのに
Road Racer GIRI
I've been focusing on overtaking NATURAL in the issue with our front cover spot,
巻頭カラーの号
「NATURAL」に勝ちたいって気持ちばかりだったけど
but it looks like we have Fukuda and Takahama to worry about, too!
福田さんや高浜さんも絡んできそうだな
The manuscript with the cover spread has already been sent to the presses.
もう巻頭カラーの原稿は入稿してるんだ どうこう考えてもしかたないだろ
No amount of worrying will do us any good now.
You're right.
そうだな やるだけやったし 今やってる原稿に全力
We've done what we can,
so let's focus on the manuscript we're doing now!
Hattori?
服部さん
We've been had!
やられた
J-Just look at this!
と とにかく見てくれ
The sample copy with our front cover spread?
巻頭カラーの見本誌
Look at NATURAL!
「NATURAL」だ
What? This is supposed to be NATURAL, right?
えっ これ 「NATURAL」ですよね な 何で
Wh-What's...
Crow doing there?!
クロウが出てる
mogakinagara saikou no yume wo
The times when I fight and struggle and dream
我喜欢奋斗着将最棒的梦想
katachi ni suru kono shunkan ga suki sa
of all the things I want in life is the best
打造成型的这个瞬间
tatakau you na te wo tsunagu you na
That's when I feel the bond between us and our strength to fight
如战斗般     把双手紧握
kankaku ga shigekiteni da ne
Our view of the world overlaps and stimulates us
感觉   (交错着)   非常刺激
kousa shite
dakara motto migakou jibun rashiku arou
Let us polish ourselves, be more like how we should be
所以更加磨练     保持自我
tsuzuita michi ni aru hazu
The future can be found on the path we walk
mirai wa
(未来)  应该有延续的道路
shinzuru mono ga chigau nakamatachi
My comrades believe in different things than me
信念各异的同伴们
Rival...and Friend!
Rival..and Friend!
butsukariau Pride
Our pride clashes
相互碰撞  Pride
yuzurenai kore kara mo kokoro no mama susumou yo
I can't give up on it, I have to do what my heart commands me to do
决不妥协   从今往后也按着心意前进
junbi wa dekita
I'm ready
准备好了
ikki ni kakeagaru tame no
I've got the unbending pride
为了一鼓作气前行的
akiramenai Pride
to run to the top now
决不放弃 Pride
hisshi nanda yo suki dakara suki wo mune ni susumu n da
This is my only choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
拼了命的  因为喜欢  就让喜欢在心里成长
donna ashita ga matteru ka shiranai
I don't know what tomorrow will be like
不知道有怎样的明天在等待着
asu mo
But I know that tomorrow, again,
(明天也)   我们还是会   (不遗余力)
bokura wa
girigiri
ganbatteru darou
we will do our best to get by
竭尽全力吧
Next Time
Preview
If they don't try harder, PCP will be in trouble.
頑張らないと PCPやばいぞ
There's nothing to worry about.
大丈夫です
Ashirogi always surpass my expectations.
亜城木君たちはいつも僕の思惑を超えてくる
I'll surpass myself!
俺は俺を超えるぜ
Next time: Last and Password.
Last and
Password
Just keep thinking about it,
考えて考え抜けば夢に繋がる道が見つかる
and you'll find the path that leads to your dreams!